Finding Aid for the Collection of Broadside Ballads from England, Ireland, and the United States LSC.0605
UCLA Library Special Collections
- England
  - Pitts, John (Affectionate-Cabin), ca. 1802-1844
    - Bewildered maid: or, Slow broke the light. Brandon, Isaac, The bewildered maid: or, Slow broke the light. London, England; Pitts Printer, Wholesale Toy and Marble warehouse 6, Great st. Andrew street, 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:4:21; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 24 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Bit of the brown. A bit of the brown. London, England; Printed and sold by J. Pitts 6. Great st. Andrew street 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:5:7; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 24 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Blackbird. Upton, William, fl. 1778, Blackbird. London, England; Pitts, Printer, Wholesale Toy and marble Warehouse, Great St. Andrew Street, 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:5:9; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Blackbird. Upton, William, fl. 1778, Blackbird. London, England; Pitts Printer Toy and Marble Warehouse 6 st Andrew st 7dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:5:10; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Bleak was the morn: or, The sailor's return. Dibdin, Charles, 1745-1814, Bleak was the morn: or, The sailor's return. London, England; Printed and sold by J. Pitts 6 Great st Andrews street 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:5:14; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Blue ey'd Mary. Blue ey'd Mary. London, England; J. Pitts Printer, Toy and Marble Warehouse, 6 Great st. Andrew Street 7 dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:6:4; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 23 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Bold boatswain of Dover. The bold boatswain of Dover. London, England; Pitts Printer Wholesale Toy & Marble Warehouse 6 Great st Andrew street 7 dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:6:12; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 24 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Bold Forty Second. The bold Forty Second. London, England; Printed and sold by J. Pitts 14 Andrew street, 7 dials, [between 1802 and 1819]., Shelfmark: 3:6:15; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Bold Irishman. The bold Irishman. London, England; Pitts Printer wholesale Toy & Marble Ware[house 6] Great st. Andrew street, 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:6:17; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Braes of Birnibouzle. Braes of Birnibouzle. London, England; J. Pitts Printer and Toy Warehouse, Great st. Andrew street 7 dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:7:7; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 24 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Braham's Beautiful maid. Liston's Beautiful maid: a popular burlesque parody. Dibdin, Thomas, 1771-1841, Braham's Beautiful maid. London, England; Pitts Printer and Toy Warehouse 6 Great st. Andrew Street 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:7:8; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Braham's Beautiful maid. Liston's Beautiful maid: a popular burlesque parody. Liston, Harry, Liston's Beautiful maid: a popular burlesque parody. London, England; Pitts Printer and Toy Warehouse 6 Great st. Andrew Street 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:7:8; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Britain's guardian angel. Thomson, James, 1700-1748, Britain's guardian angel. London, England; Published at J. Pitts Toy & marble Warehouse Great st Andrew street 7 dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:7:15; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Cabin boy. Dibdin, Thomas, 1771-1841, The cabin boy. London, England; Pitts Printer, and Wholesale Toy Warehouse Great st. Andrew Street 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:8:10; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Pitts, John (Captain-Covent), ca. 1802-1844
    - Captain Bell. Hazel Dean. Bottle of rum. Bottle of rum. London, England; Pitts, Printer, wholesale Toy and marble warehouse, 6, Gt. St. Andrews Street, Seven Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:8:14; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Captain Bell. Hazel Dean. Bottle of rum. Hazel Dean. London, England; Pitts, Printer, wholesale Toy and marble warehouse, 6, Gt. St. Andrews Street, Seven Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:8:14; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Captain Bell. Hazel Dean. Bottle of rum. Captain Bell. London, England; Pitts, Printer, wholesale Toy and marble warehouse, 6, Gt. St. Andrews Street, Seven Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:8:14; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Careless Billy. Careless Billy. London, England; Printed and sold by J. Pitts, No. 14 Great St. Andrew Street. Seven Dials, [between 1802 and 1819]., Shelfmark: 3:8:17; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Castilian maid. Moore, Thomas, 1779-1852, The Castilian maid. London, England; Pitts, Printer Toy & Marble Warehouse 6, Great st. Andrew street, 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:9:4; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Celia's complaint, for the loss of her shepherd, gone to fight in America. Celia's complaint, for the loss of her shepherd, gone to fight in America. London, England; Printed & sold by J. Pitts Great St. Andrew Street, Seven Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:9:11; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Chorus of huntsmen in Der Freitscuhz [sic]. Kind, Friedrich, 1768-1843, Chorus of huntsmen in Der Freitscuhz [sic]. London, England; Pitts Printer Wholesale Toy & Marble Wharehouse [sic], 6 Gt. St. Andrew Street 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:10:5; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Chorus of huntsmen in Der Freitscuhz [sic]. Kind, Friedrich, 1768-1843, Chorus of huntsmen in Der Freitscuhz [sic]. London, England; Pitts Printer Wholesale Toy & Marble Wharehouse [sic], 6 Gt. St. Andrew Street 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:10:6; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Cold winter is past. Cold winter is past. London, England; Pitts printer, wholesale Toy and Marble warehouse, 5, Great st Andrew street 7 dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:11:6; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Come where the aspens quiver. The new mariners. Come where the aspens quiver. London, England; Pitts, Printer, wholesale Toy and Marble warehouse, 6, Gt. St. Andrew Street, Seven Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:12:4; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Come where the aspens quiver. The new mariners. Dudley, H. Bate (Henry Bate), Sir, 1745-1824, The new mariners. London, England; Pitts, Printer, wholesale Toy and Marble warehouse, 6, Gt. St. Andrew Street, Seven Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:12:4; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Contented wife. The contented wife. London, England; Printed and sold by J. Pitts, 14, Andrew street, 7 dials, [between 1802 and 1819]., Shelfmark: 3:12:8; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Corinthian's diary. Corinthian's diary. London, England; J Pitts, Printer Wholesale Toy & Marble Warehouse, 6, Great st. Andrew-street, 7 dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:13:1; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Corporal Casey. Colman, George, 1762-1836, Corporal Casey. London, England; Pitts, Printer, wholesale Toy and Marble warehouse. 6, Great St. Andrew Street, Seven Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:13:3; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 17 × 8 cm. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Cottage in the grove. Hook, Mr. (James), 1746-1827, The cottage in the grove. London, England; Pitts, Printer, Wholesale toy and Marble Warehouse 6 Great st. Andrew street, 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:13:8; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 24 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Country girl. The country girl. London, England; [P]rinted at J. Pitts, Wholesale Toy Warehouse, Great st. Andrew Street, 7 Dials, [between 1802 and 1819]., Shelfmark: 3:13:13; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 24 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Covent Garden ramble. Covent Garden ramble. London, England; J. Pitts, Printer, 6 Great st. Andrew street 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:13:19; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Pitts, John (Cupid-England), ca. 1802-1844
    - Cupid the pretty plough boy. Cupid the pretty plough boy. London, England; Pitts Printer, Toy and Marble warehous[e] 6, Great st, Andrew street, 7 dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:14:9; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Curly headed boy. The curly headed boy. London, England; J. Pitts, Printer and Toy Warehouse, 6, Great St. Andrew Street 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:14:13; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 24 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Curly headed plough boy. Curly headed plough boy. London, England; Pitt, Printer, Wholesale Toy and Marble Warehouse, 6, Gt. St. Andrew st., [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:15:1; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Curly headed plough boy. The curly headed plough boy. London, England; Pitts, Printer, Wholesale Toy and Marble Warehouse, 6, Great st Andrew Street 7 dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:15:2; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 24 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Dandy bonnet. The dandy bonnet. London, England; Pitts, Printer. Toy and Marble Warehouse, 6. Great st. Andrew street 7 dial, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:15:7; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Dauntless sailor. The dauntless sailor. London, England; Printed and sold by J. Pitts, 6, Great st. Andrew street 7 dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:15:10; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Dear Mary: or, Farewell to old England. Thompson, Edward, 1738?-1786, Dear Mary: or, Farewell to old England. London, England; Printed and Sold by J Pitts, No. 14, Great St. Andrew Street, 7 Dials, [between 1802 and 1819]., Shelfmark: 3:15:17; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Deep deep sea. The Indian maid. The deep deep sea. London, England; Pitts, Printer, wholesale Toy and Marble warehouse 6, Gt. St. Andrew Street, Seven Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:16:9; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Deep deep sea. The Indian maid. The Indian maid. London, England; Pitts, Printer, wholesale Toy and Marble warehouse 6, Gt. St. Andrew Street, Seven Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3:16:9; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Dick the dustman. Dibdin, Charles, 1745-1814, Dick the dustman. London, England; Printed and sold by J. 14, Great st, Andrew street, 7 Dials, [between 1802 and 1819]., Shelfmark: v; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Disconsolate lover. The disconsolate lover. London, England; Printed at J. Pitts, Wholesale Toy and Marble Warehouse, 6 Great st Andrew stree[t], 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3.17.2; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Drinking song. Drinking song. London, England; Printed and sold by J. Pitts, 14, Great st Andr [sic] street, 7 dials, [between 1802 and 1819]., Shelfmark: 3.18.6; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Drum major. Drum major. London, England; Printed and sold by J. Pitts 14, Great St Andrew Street, Seven Dials, [between 1802 and 1819]., Shelfmark: 3.18.7; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Duett all's well. Dibdin, Thomas, 1771-1841, Duett all's well. London, England; Printed and sold by J. Pitts, 6 Great st Andrew street, 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 3.18.13; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Ellen Aureen. Mazzinghi, Joseph, 1765-1844, Ellen Aureen. London, England; Pitts, Printer, Wholesale Toy & Marble house, 6, Graa [sic] St. Andrew Street, 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 4.1.9; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Elopement of pretty Polly. The elopement of pretty Polly. London, England; Printed and sold by J. Pitts, 14 Great St Andrew Street, Seven Dials, [between 1802 and 1819]., Shelfmark: 4.1.14; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - England's gallant sailor king. A monody. A monody. London, England; Pitts, Printer, and Toy Warehouse, 6 Great St, Andrew Street Seven Dials, [1837]., Shelfmark: 4.2.7; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - England's gallant sailor king. A monody. England's gallant sailor king. London, England; Pitts, Printer, and Toy Warehouse, 6 Great St, Andrew Street Seven Dials, [1837]., Shelfmark: 4.2.7; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Pitts, John (Erin-Funny), ca. 1802-1844
    - Erin-go-bragh. The thumping glass of gin. The thumping glass of gin. London, England; [Pitts, Printers, wholesale toy and marble warehouse, 6, Great St Andrew Street, Seven Dials], [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 4.2.13; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 11 cm. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Erin-go-bragh. The thumping glass of gin. Erin-go-bragh. London, England; [Pitts, Printers, wholesale toy and marble warehouse, 6, Great St Andrew Street, Seven Dials], [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 4.2.13; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 11 cm. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Exploits of Teddy Blink, and Bandy Jack. Exploits of Teddy Blink, and Bandy Jack. London, England; Pitts, Printer, Wholesale Toy and Marble Warehouse, 6, Great St Andrew Street, 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 4.3.10; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Fair Ellen. Dibdin, Thomas, 1771-1841, Fair Ellen. London, England; Printed and sold by J. Pitts, 14 Great St Andrew Street, Seven Dials, [between 1802 and 1819]., Shelfmark: 4.4.4; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Fair Evelyn's bower. Fair Evelyn's bower. London, England; Printed and sold by J. Pitts, 6 Great st Andrew seven Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 4.4.5; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Faithful Henry. Faithful Henry. London, England; Printed and sold by J. Pitts, 14, Great St. Andrew-Street, Seven Dials, [between 1802 and 1819]., Shelfmark: 4.4.12; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Fashions: or, Farmer Stump's journey to London. The fashions: or, Farmer Stump's journey to London. London, England; J. Pitts, Printer, 14 Great st Andrew Street, 7 Dials, [between 1802 and 1819]., Shelfmark: 4.5.2; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Fate of poor Anna. Fate of poor Anna. London, England; Printed for and sold by J. Pitts, No. 14, Great St. Andrew Street, Seven Dials, [between 1802 and 1817]., Shelfmark: 4.5.4; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Fighting day. The fighting day. London, England; Printed and3old [sic] by J. Pitts, Great St [A]ndrew Street, Seven Dials, [between 1802 and 1819]., Shelfmark: 4.5.15; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Flashy back and hungry belly. Hudson, Thomas, Flashy back and hungry belly. London, England; Printed at J. Pitt's Wholesale Toy and Marble Warehouse, 6, Great St. Andrew Street, 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 4.6.5; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Foot of the hill. Foot of the hill. London, England; J. Pitts, Printer, 6 Great st Andrew Street, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 4.6.13; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - For tenderness form'd. For tenderness form'd. London, England; Printed for and sold by J. Pitts, No. 14, Great St Andrew Street, Seven Dials, [between 1802 and 1817]., Shelfmark: 4.6.16; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Forecastle sailor: or, Guardian Frigate. The forecastle sailor: or, Guardian Frigate. London, England; J. Pitts, Printer, 6 Great St Andrew Street, 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 4.6.17; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Forsaken maid. The forsaken maid. London, England; J. Pitts, 14 Great St Andrew-street, Seven Dials, [between 1802 and 1819]., Shelfmark: 4.7.2; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Four and twenty fidlers. D'Urfey, Thomas, 1653-1723, Four and twenty fidlers. London, England; J. Pitts, Printer, 14 Great St Andrew Stree[t], Seven Dials, [between 1802 and 1819]., Shelfmark: 4.7.5; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Fox chase. The fox chase. London, England; Printed at J. Pitts, Wholesale Toy and Marble Warehous[e], 6, Great st Andrew street, 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 4.7.6; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Friend and bottle. Friend and bottle. London, England; Pitts, Printer, wholesale Toy and Marble warehouse, 6, Gt. St. Andrew-Street, Seven Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 4.7.8; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 12 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Friendship out of fashion. Friendship out of fashion. London, England; Printed and sold by J. Pitts, No. 14, Great St. Andrew Street, Seven Dials, [between 1802 and 1819]., Shelfmark: 4.7.10; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - From night till morn I take my glass. From night till morn I take my glass. London, England; Printed for and sold by J. Pitts, 14, Great Saint Andrew Street, Seven Dials, [between 1802 and 1817]., Shelfmark: 4.7.11; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Fuddling day: or, Saint Monday. The fuddling day: or, Saint Monday. London, England; Printed and sold by J. Pitts, 14, Great St. Andrew Street, Seven Dials, [between 1802 and 1819]., Shelfmark: 4.7.12; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Funny eye: or, Female fashions. Funny eye: or, Female fashions. London, England; Printed and sold by J. Pitts, 6, Great St Andrew Street, Seven Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 4.7.16; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Pitts, John (Gallant-Grand), ca. 1802-1844
    - Gallant sailor. The gallant sailor. London, England; Pitts, Printer, Toy and Marble Warehouse, 6, Great [S]t Andrew Street, 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 4.8.4; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engraving); 24 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Gardengate [sic]. The gardengate [sic]. London, England; Pitts, Printer, Wholesale Toy and marble warehouse, 6 Great st. Andrew street, 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 4.8.15; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Generous farmer: or, Poor soldier. The generous farmer: or, Poor soldier. London, England; Printed at Pitts Wholesale Toy Warehouse, 6, Great St Andrew Street, 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 4.9.6; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 11 cm. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Ghost of Maria. The ghost of Maria. London, England; Printed for and sold by J. Pitts, 14, Great Saint Andrew Street, Seven Dials, [between 1802 and 1817]., Shelfmark: 4.9.11; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Gipsy loddy. Gipsy loddy. London, England; Pitts, Printer Toy and Marble Warehouse, 6, Great St Andrew Street, 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 4.9.12; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Golden glove. The golden glove. London, England; Pitts, Printer, wholesale toy and marble warehouse, 6, Great St. Andrew-street, Seven-dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 4.10.13; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 24 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Good and bad wives. Good and bad wives. London, England; J. Pitts, Printer, 14 Great St Adrew [sic] street, 7 Dials, [between 1802 and 1819]., Shelfmark: 4.11.5; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Good humour'd fellow. The good humour'd fellow. London, England; Printed & sold by J. Pitts, 14 Great St. Andrew street, 7 Dials, [between 1802 and 1819]., Shelfmark: 4.11.6; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Good Lord Fauconbridge's generous gift. Good Lord Fauconbridge's generous gift. London, England; Pitts, printer & Wholesale Toy Warehouse, 6 Great st. Andrew Street, 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 4.11.8; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Gossiping husband. The gossiping husband. London, England; Pitts, Printer, wholesale Toy and Marble warehouse, 6, Gt. St. Andrews Street, Seven Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 4.11.17; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 24 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Gossiping wife. The gossiping wife. London, England; Pitts, Printer, wholesale Toy and Marble warehouse, 6, Gt. St. Andrews [sic] Street, Seven Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 4.11.20; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 24 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Gown of green. The gown of green. London, England; Pitts, Printer, Wholesale Toy & Marble Warehouse, 6, Great St. Andrew Street, 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 4.12.1; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 24 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Grageral Macgree. Grageral Macgree. London, England; Pitts, Printer, Wholesale Toy & Marble Warehouse, 6, Great st. Andrew street, 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 4.12.2; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Grand chorus of huntsmen in Der Frieschutz [sic]. Kind, Friedrich, 1768-1843, The grand chorus of huntsmen in Der Frieschutz [sic]. London, England; Pitts Printer Wholesale Marble & Toy Wharehouse [sic], 6, Gt. [S]t. Andrew Street 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 4.12.8; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Grand chorus of huntsmen in Der Frieschutz [sic]. Kind, Friedrich, 1768-1843, The grand chorus of huntsmen in Der Frieschutz [sic]. London, England; Pitts Printer Wholesale Marble & Toy Wharehouse [sic], 6, Gt. [S]t. Andrew Street 7 Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 4.12.6; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 9 cm. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Grand conversation under the rose. The grand conversation under the rose. London, England; Pitts, Printer, wholesale Toy and Marble warehouse, 6 Gt St. Andrews [sic] street, Seven Dials, [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 4.12.15; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 11 cm. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Pitts, John (Greenland-Howls), ca. 1802-1844
    - Greenland whale fishery. Greenland whale fishery. [London], [England], [between 1819 and 1844]., Shelfmark: 4.13.14; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 24 × 10 cm. (Box 5, Folder 6)